[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I’m breaking up with you.
What?
How are you feeling, Kierra?
I feel like I’m trapped in two places.
I want to breathe.
How are you?
I'm really okay.
I want that love that you guys have for each other.
Someday you will find that someone.
I can't wait for that someday to come.
Who are you?
Ciandrei.
Ciandrei Kyle is my name.
But you can call me Shan.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Kiss me.
It was just a one-night stand, and it won't happen again.
And I won't see that guy again anyway.
Attack the monsters!
I was so afraid of monsters growing up.
I tried to be brave and fight them,
but sometimes I wonder...
What if there's a little monster inside me too?
I hope there isn't.
I don't want to be like them.
Shan!
Did you break this?
Dad…
Didn't I tell you not to mess with my stuff?
Huh?
No, Dad.
What do you mean no?
Mommy…
You’re gonna cry on me now? Huh?
You're just like your mom.
Go to your room,
and don't come out while I'm here.
Hurry up!
I didn't do anything wrong.
It wasn't me who broke it.
Hiro?
Shan!
What are you doing here?
Let's play.
I'm bored.
I can’t go out of my room.
Is your door locked?
Wait, I'll be right back.
What's that?
Didn't you say your door is locked?
But the window is open.
Jump!
It's too high.
Bring your pillows, protect your head like this, and roll.
Okay!
You can do it.
Jump!
Roel,
Hiro,
- hide! - let's go!
Hiro!
Dad already left,
wait for me!
Sure!
Hiro!
‘Sup?
Over there.
- Okay! - Come on. Hurry!
Let's play over there at Valley Golf.
He ran away because of you.
What did you do?
Why are you blaming me?
He ran away because of you.
You're always not here.
Why are you blaming me, huh?
- Mom! - Don’t you dare touch me.
Shan!
Baby, where did you go?
You got me so worried.
I just went out with Hiro.
Wait, dear.
What's that? What happened there?
Shan, is there something you want to tell mommy?
No, I just bumped into something.
Mom, you won't leave me, right?
Of course not, my dear.
You know I love you, right?
Okay?
Come on, let's go inside. Let's eat.
You have school early tomorrow.
You need to sleep early.
And you really had me so worried.
I think my dad's driver is nearby.
Want a ride home?
Don't you want to go home yet?
I'll stay here at school for now.
Is it because of the monster again?
Okay. From now on, I'll go with you, too.
You’ll do that for me?
Of course! I'm your best friend.
Is that Acel?
Hey!
What’s wrong with you?
We're gonna tell the teachers on you.
You guys are bullies!
Hey!
What?
We're just asking for his notebook.
Just go away.
Let's go.
Jerks.
You okay?
Next time, you can come play with us so those bullies don't come back.
Thank you, but what if you guys aren't here?
Tell the teachers or your parents.
My dad always tells me to tell him whenever someone makes me cry at school.
But what if the person making you cry isn't in your class?
Do you tell your dad, too?
I will always tell my dad.
Can I tell your dad about my problems, too?
Why? Is someone making you cry?
No.
She’s already six, and she wants to meet her dad.
Erin—
we’ll get an annulment.
You’re married?
Alfred, you told me you were just abroad.
How dare you! This is so unfair.
I don't deserve this! Elyse doesn't deserve this!
Erin, Erin. Please listen to me.
Ciana and I will... we’ll get an annulment,
She's just waiting for Shan to finish high school.
But honestly, that bitch is still in love with her ex!
That's why I want this to end, too.
What are you doing at school?
Huh?
Are you even studying?
Dad, 93 is my lowest grade.
And you're proud of that? Huh? 93?
And you're talking back too.
You're happy with your 93? Huh?
Come here, stand up.
You're just wasting your tuition fee!
And how dare you talk back to me?
93? You're satisfied with that? Huh?
Dad. It hurts.
Are you so stubborn that you don't want to study?
Ouch.
What?
Huh!
You’re gonna talk back again?
93, huh!
Sir, sir. That's enough. He's just a kid.
Does it hurt?
Come here, I'll help you up.
I'll get you a seat.
You good?
Yes.
Are those your grades?
Can I see?
They're really high.
You're actually doing well.
Good job.
Does your dad always do this?
Well, it's just...
Dad's just angry.
Anyway, from now on I'll look out for you, okay?
Is that okay with you?
Good job.
From that day on,
Roel was always looking out for me.
Did you think I didn't know what you were doing?
We became close.
- You've got some nerve! - Speak for yourself!
You have a bastard child!
How many years have you been hiding this?
And you? How many years have you been hiding yours?
And how many times did you bring your man here, to my house?
You act as if you don't bring women here.
Did you think I didn't know?
You cheated first.
You made me do this.
Who knows? Maybe I'm not even Shan's father.
What?
What did you say?
I said, "maybe it's your son with that stupid guy,” you bitch!
How dare you!
You can say whatever you want about me, but don't you dare drag my son into this!
Loser! Liar! You're a liar! No one will ever love you!
Go ahead! Go ahead, hurt me!
We are leaving this house, and I am taking our son with me.
Go ahead! Do whatever you want to do. Leave!
You are the one desperately trying to stay in this fucking marriage.
Because you're afraid Shan will discover all your bullshit!
Shan!
Shan! We’re leaving!
Roel, I need to say goodbye to my friends.
Can you drop me off at their house?
I'll tell them myself.
You promise?
Promise.
Shan, let's go.
We're leaving tonight. Come on.
Come on, let’s go.
My mother promised me a perfect family.
But it was a lie.
And soon,
we left Dad.
I moved to Bataan with Mom and her boyfriend, Uncle James.
Many things had changed in my life at such an early age.
I struggled to be happy.
Okay. Thank you, Attorney.
The annulment is in process.
Oh, thank you.
Uncle James was making an effort to get closer to me.
Wow! Shan, that's great!
Is this Science?
That’s a perfect score.
You’re right.
Wow.
Good job.
But I found it very hard to open up.
I built a wall around me.
It's okay.
He's still adjusting.
Wait…
Do you think it would be a good idea to go on a beach trip?
He loves the beach.
And maybe we can bond there.
Of course.
Let’s go there this weekend. I know a good resort here in Bataan.
Thank you so much for being so patient with my son.
Our son.
And just like I promised you,
I will do everything to earn Shan's trust and love.
Even if it takes time.
Uncle James treated me like his own son.
My relationship with him was starting to get better.
I was starting to accept my new life with him and Mom.
But then came a day I will never forget.
Yes, dear. Are you okay?
Mom, how much longer are you going to be?
We're on our way home, but we've run into a small problem.
But we've already enrolled you at Lopez High.
Really? Thank you!
Yes, my dear. But we’re sorry, okay?
We didn't wake you up earlier because we left early to avoid the traffic.
Are you all right there?
Yes, Mom. I'm fine.
Wait for us, okay? We're almost there.
We'll eat together.
Okay. Be careful.
Okay, see you later. I love you, son.
We love you, Shan. Never ever forget that.
Never ever. Love you, Mom. Uncle, too.
Take care!
See you, dear.
Mom…
No, no, no!
No!
I cried every day after the accident.
When my mom passed away,
I felt like half of me was buried with her
and the other half was buried in sadness.
I blame myself.
If I hadn't wanted to study in Manila,
it wouldn't have happened.
Mom and Uncle James would still be here.
Shan, cheer up.
You should eat. You haven't eaten in days.
You'll get sick.
They’re your new family, Shan.
She's your new sister, Elyse.
Hi, Shan.
I'm Auntie Erin.
I'm Elyse's mom.
I have something for you. Wait, I'll just get it.
Stay with dad for now, okay.
Thank you.
Hi, Shan—
She didn't mean to.
Are you okay?
Yes, Dad. I’m okay.
I'll just call the maid to clean that up.
Hold on.
Shan, what are you doing?
Homework.
What are you doing?
In my room?
Hi, kids!
Look, I brought you some snacks.
I'll just leave it here. Eat when you're hungry.
Thank you, Mom.
Shan, let’s eat!
Shan, I have something for you.
I noticed you like toy figures, so I got that for you.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
You kids eat now. I'll get the tray when you're done.
Thank you.
Okay.
Shan, are you going to eat your cookies?
If not, can I eat them?
You can eat it with me.
Shan, can we always eat together?
At the classroom earlier.
There he is.
Hey.
I'm sorry Shan, I didn't know that's what happened.
I should've reached out more.
Wait.
Was he the monster you were talking about when we were kids?
Yeah.
I wish it were just like the toys we played with when we were young,
where one swing of the sword and the monster's gone, but—
I'm stuck with him for now.
Shan, you've been really strong all these years
Shan, how's your step-mom? Step-sister?
Honestly, they’ve been nice.
I actually like being an older brother to my sister.
And she's always bugging me, but she's the
only one I can really talk to in that house.
I like having her in that hell house.
That's good, right? At least you know we're here to support you always.
Anything you need, we'll be here.
Of course.
Okay.
But, I can't wait to get out of that house.
I want to go to college already.
What?
What do you mean?
We just started high school.
I’m just looking forward to that freedom.
Freedom?
What kind of freedom?
Here it is!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Three! - Three!
- Two! - Two!
- One! - One!
Shot!
One— Three, four—
- Cheers! - Cheers!
I’m sorry, I have to go.
Shan, please.
Can we just try something real, please?
Can we just be together?
Just us?
Come on, let's make it official already.
Just tell me, what's wrong with me?
Why can't I just be enough for you?
I already told you before…
I'm not the type of guy who commits.
If you think I'm going to change my mind,
I won't.
I'm sorry, I won't.
But we're so cute together.
I already posted you on my socials, what am I gonna do now?
What am I supposed to do now? You were my first, remember?
I was going to introduce you to my family.
We were supposed to go home to the province together, weren't we?
I can change for you.
Huh? What do you want? What do you want? Huh?
Just pick me. Just me.
I have to go. Okay?
- I have to leave. I have to leave - Please don't leave.
I didn't know freedom could also taste this bad, but I didn't care.
And how about now, Shan?
How are you feeling?
Still the same.
Enjoying my freedom.
And by freedom, you mean?
Freedom from my dad.
Freedom from my past.
From all the painful things that happened.
Is it really freedom, or are you escaping?
What's the difference?
For me, they're both the same.
Not really.
For freedom, you willfully choose it.
Escaping means you’re avoiding something.
Then maybe I’m avoiding.
Avoiding doesn’t mean you’re free.
It means, you still haven’t let go.
I'm not the type of guy who commits.
Let me guess, girl number 1,569.
Fuck you. You're exaggerating, asshole.
Shan, the heartbreaker.
Someday, you'll meet your match.
Can’t wait for that!
This guy, you know—
This is mine.
Don't worry, it's free.
And next time, you can be the one to treat me to an ice cream.
There won't be a next time.
There will be.
Trust me.
Truth or dare?
Dare.
Kiss me.
What the fuck…
Hi, miss.
Woah. Relax.
I just wanna know your name.
Let go, man.
Okay, okay.
Are you okay?
I told you we'd see each other again.
Sorry, do I know you?
Oh, I’m sorry. Do you want me to remind you?
Hey.
Are you really okay?
I’m fine!
I don’t think you’re okay.
Come on, I’ll walk you back to your table.
No, I can handle myself.
Besides, you're just a stranger to me.
You really don't remember?
But you know what?
Actually, you didn't have to pay for my service that night.
What?
Honestly, it was kind of offensive.
But I'll let it slide.
Because you did buy me breakfast.
Delicious, by the way.
Sevi, where are you? Come pick me up.
I’m in BGC. Did something happen?
Where are you? I'll come get you.
No, I'll just go there.
I'm in BGC too.
Send me your location.
No!
You send me your location.
Okay, fine. Thanks.
Get a room.
Such a buzzkill.
You know, you don't have to watch. It's awkward.
Do whatever you want. I don't care.
Wait, you still haven't told me your name.
You don't deserve to know.
Besides, with all the girls you've been with,
you won't remember it tomorrow anyway.
I don't think so.
Kierra.
Turns out we have a common friend.
So you were studying in España?
Wait. Let me guess.
Architecture?
How did you know? You're so creepy.
Wait. Are you in college?
No.
I'm in law school.
Really?
Yeah.
I graduated psychology and then—
took a gap year for fun, but now I decided to enter law school.
It seemed challenging, and I love challenges.
You’d know, right?
Because we're the same.
We're not the same.
I don't make out with girls in public.
First, it was just one girl.
Second, in public?
Don't worry.
I prefer doing it in private.
My bad, I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing to me?
Well, because it seems like you don't like me kissing other girls.
I mean, I won't do it again if you say so.
I didn't know you were the jealous type.
Hey, by the way…
Have you been sleeping well lately?
Ke!
Sorry, sorry, I got lost.
Master's drunk, so I came to pick you up instead.
Do you know that guy?
- Is he bothering you? - No. Um—
I was just surprised. He came up suddenly. Let's go.
Wait.
Let me just put this on.
This is new, right?
Yeah. Thanks.
Wait.
It’s Master, hold on.
Master.
Hey!
Yeah, I've got Ke with me.
Fuck you, Lavin.
If Kierra doesn't get home safe and sound, don't you dare come in tomorrow.
I'll smash your head in. You better take care of her, Lavin.
Yes sir, Master. Affirmative! Ten-four!
Good. I’ll get you chicken wings tomorrow. ‘Kay, bye.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey, thanks for bringing me home.
- Yeah, yeah, no problem. - Take care.
Yeah. Message me.
Okay. Sure.
You’re fucking kidding me, Kierra.
You’re fucking kidding me.
Are you playing with me?
Are you messing with me?
You know that person likes you.
Not only did you not keep your distance, you even had him drop you off.
Fuck, you're such a slut. You're such a slut.
- You're such a slut, fuck you. - Miguel... People are watching.
Get in the car. Get in, get in.
I said get inside, Kierra.
Get in the fucking car.
Do you want to get hurt?
- Do you want to get hurt? - That's enough…
Enough—
For here or to go?
To go.
Please wait for your change.
Here.
Please wait by the side.
Good morning.
Welcome to Yesterday’s Coffee.
What can I get for you?
Order for Kierra.
Enjoy.
Don’t be so grumpy in the morning, Kierra. Have a great day.
Sugar.
What is it about you that I can’t ignore?
- Hey! Surprise! - Hello!
Hi, Shan!
Your interests have really changed now, Shan.
From parties and sleeping around—
Don't waste your time on guys like me.
Hey!
You've been focusing on law school now and this business.
Good— Are you okay?
I don't think you need some coffee.
It looks like sleep is what you need.
Of all the baristas I've met,
you're the only one who sticks your nose in my business.
What if after our one-night stand,
I ask you to go out on a date—
with me?
What would you say?
Even without the one-night stand, I wouldn't date you.
Admit it, you're cheating on me.
Didn't I tell you to stay away from him?
You're safe here, Kierra.
Let's go somewhere else.
MkvDrama.net